

Banashankari Stage II Bengaluru, INDIA 560070 ▼ WHC9+8C BSK

Pvthon 3

& varungupta3009

| Experience Skill |
|--|
| JavaScript Experience Skill |
| C/C++ Experience Skill |
| Windows 7/8/10 Experience Skill |
| Frontend Design and Development Experience Skill |
| Full-Stack Web Development Experience Skill |
| Angular (TS), React (JS/TS) Experience Skill |
| WordPress, CMS Experience Skill |
| Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator Experience Skill |
| Adobe After Effects and Premiere Pro Experience Skill |
| Blender, Pixar Renderman Experience Skill |
| Cloud Architechture (GCP) Experience Skill |

Experience

Global IT: Data and Reporting Analyst

Hewlett Packard Enterprise Feb 2021 - Present (3 mos)

Student Lead in Network Security and Web Development

Developer Student Clubs • PES University Jan 2019 - Sep 2020 (1 yr 9 mos)



Penetration Tester

Center for Information Security, Forensics and Cyber Resilience May 2020 - Sep 2020 (5 mos)



Software Engineer

Mindtree

Jul 2019 - Feb 2020 (8 mos)

Education



PES University

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science & Engineering 2017 - 2021



R. V. PU College

Pre-University, Affiliated to NCERT, New Delhi, Computer Science



Carmel School, Padmanabhanagar

ICSE, New Delhi — SSLC, Karnataka

Publications & Awards

Software Implementation of an Automatic Movable Road Barrier IEEE, October 2019, ISBN: 978-1-7281-1576-4

Prof. C N R Rao Merit Scholarship

PES University, November 2019

Languages

English Hindi Kannada

Hobbies

Reading

Gaming

X Virtual Aviation

伽 Music

About me

I am a programmer and experienced web-developer, fluent in Python, C++, C#, Go with over 9 years of experience in Python and C++, and moderately versed in 7 other languages. I am a polymath and love to explore and try new technologies and fiddling with anything related to computers or the Windows OS in general. I am also a graphics designer and a hobbyist hacker.

I recommend checking out my LinkedIn Profile for real-time accurate information, to stay regularly updated, and to get in touch with me instantly.

